How to use the print on the pattern?
It is very difficult for the client to understand the final effect of the print on the pattern.
Previously, we used to sell the print in silver or make the existing pattern online,
and then fill in the effect to show it to the client.
In this case, it is both time-consuming and labor-intensive, and it is not intuitive.
It is difficult to determine the final size.
Now, we can show it to the client directly and efficiently.
Like this, this is the final effect of the print on the pattern we want to show to the client.
This way, it is more intuitive and can directly know the final size.
I am a designer from Kaixin.
My daily work is to design and develop with the client's needs.
As a designer,
the most painful thing in my previous work is to communicate with the client.
The client's understanding of the pattern is often biased,
and it is difficult to convert the designer's feeling in the communication.
It is often necessary to wait for the sample to be made and then communicate and modify it face-to-face.
Now that we have 3D, the whole process becomes very simple.
With 70% of the design, we can directly confirm it through 3D,
make a precise sample, and quickly recommend it to the client.
We can even do a quick version for some clients.
Or we can use 3D to make a 3D design
that can be directly confirmed by 3D and the client designer.
I believe that in the future, 3D will help us to work more simply and easily.
I am a designer from Kaixin.
I am mainly responsible for 3D production in France.
I used to need a week to make a sample,
but now I can make a 3D in one or two hours.
I can send it directly to them to confirm.
It is more convenient to modify,
and there is no need to waste so much manpower and physical strength.
Now that there are more 3D designs,
I can modify some of the designs myself.
The high-effectiveness of different materials is interesting to me.
I have a better understanding of some of the techniques.
I am mainly responsible for the work of a French office designer.
Due to the difference in language, professional knowledge,
geographical and cultural, and different ways of thinking,
communication has always been a big problem.
After using the 3D system,
the confirmation becomes very intuitive.
The technical problems are very easy to communicate with.
Moreover, I am very happy that the initial phase of the 3D design
has been converted into a 3D template.
The designer is very happy.
At the same time, the cost of developing the relevant fabric and sewing is significantly reduced.
The cycle of developing a style has also been shortened to several days.